productioncrate.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy | ProductionCrate.com

We take your privacy very seriously. Our commitment to your privacy and the full disclosure of how we gather information is evidence of that commitment.

This privacy policy (hereinafter “Privacy Policy”) describes how the personal information that we collect is processed. By use of the www.ProductionCrate.com website, which is owned and operated by ProductionCrate LLC, and the other websites of ProductionCrate LLC, including but not limited to, footagecrate.com, soundscrate.com, any sub-domains, and/or pages thereof (hereinafter collectively “our Platform”), you agree and accept all terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. _If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, do not access or use our Platform._

####  _Changes to Privacy Policy_

ProductionCrate LLC may change the Privacy Policy on our Platform at any time and from time to time without notice. You are cautioned to review the Privacy Policy posted on our Platform periodically. Your continued access to or use of our Platform after any such changes are posted will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to the changes.

####  _General Provisions_

We may collect and process personal information provided by you when you submit the registration form, when you respond to a survey questionnaire, when you email our support team, when you enter a competition, or when you opt-in with third-party services.

Additionally, our servers may collect statistical data including, traffic and usage data about which resources are being requested from our servers, visitors IP addresses and basic operating system details. This data does not identify you as an individual. Our Platform use cookies to maintain user logins while navigating between pages, and to personalize content delivery. If you wish to refuse to accept cookies, you may do so in your browser settings, however this will prevent you from accessing our Platform where personalized data is required.

If you have provided information to our servers that you wish to remove, please email your request to support@productioncrate.com and we will permanently delete your data within 30 days.

####  _Personal Information_

In order for you to communicate with ProductionCrate LLC, send and receive messages, and make secure transactions, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) contact data provided by you to us using an online form (such as your name, e-mail address and survey questionnaire responses); (2) transaction identification information (such as dates of successful payments and receipt numbers); and, (3) basic social media data to connect with Facebook, Google+ and YouTube (Public profile links and channel identifiers). Social media data is only received if you opt-in to connect using a social media service. If you communicate with us by e-mail or otherwise complete, send, or receive online forms or messages, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

####  _Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information_

To help protect your privacy we use encrypted connections to send and receive all session information.

We will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties.

We work diligently to ensure that we have taken all appropriate administrative and technical measures to prevent the unauthorized or unlawful use of your personally-identifiable information, and to prevent any accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, such information. We will not sell or disclose Personal Information about you to third parties except in accordance with this Privacy Policy or your written consent.

####  _No Liability_

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your Personal Information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You hereby acknowledge that ProductionCrate LLC is not responsible for any such inadvertent disclosures or any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

* * *

> Common Considerations and Data Removal Inquiries
> 
>   * We are never sent any personal login credentials to 3rd party sites or services (such as facebook or google), even if a user connects to ProductionCrate with one of those services.
>   * We are never sent any credit card information. When a transaction takes place all credit card details are securely processed and authenticated by PayPal, ApplePay or Stripe, and these platforms only transport the required information to our servers (such as receipts) upon successful payments.
>   * If you wish to have us remove any data that you have provided, email your request to [support@productioncrate.com](mailto:support@productioncrate.com) and we will delete your account and data from our servers within 30 days.
>
